https://laromita.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
La Romita School of Art, Inc. is very concerned with the privacy rights of our online visitors and customers and is committed to protecting the information collected about you. We have adopted an Online Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store, and use the information you provide while visiting any of the websites governed by this Privacy Policy (as listed below).
Application of the Privacy Policy
The website you are currently visiting is operated by La Romita School of Art, P.O. Box 58219 Washington, DC 20037. This Privacy Policy currently applies to the following website(s) operated by La Romita (collectively referred to as “La Romita Websites” or “our websites”): www.laromita.org, www.laromita.org
In the Future, if we wish to include additional websites under this Privacy Policy, we will take reasonable steps to list them above and ensure that they provide a link to this Privacy Policy.
Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to information submitted and collected online through the La Romita Websites (as listed above), and does not apply to information that may be collected by La Romita offline. In addition, this Privacy Policy does not extend to websites maintained by any affiliates or by other companies or organizations to which we link. When you link to any other sites from a website listed above, their privacy policies will apply.
Please note that by using our Websites, you signify your assent to La Romita’s Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Websites. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Please check back from time to time to ensure that you are aware of these changes. Your continued use of our Websites will signify your acceptance of the changes. This Privacy Policy reflects the law of the United States of America.
Information Collected by La Romita
In order to give you the best experience on our Websites, La Romita may collect information about your browsing patterns. Metrics passively collected include the following:
Totals of:
Hits
Files
Pages
Visits
Kilobytes transferred
The following user characteristics are also collected:
Unique Access sites
URLS accessed
User referrer
User agent
Hit Responsible Codes
Entry Page
Exit Page
Hostname
Search String
User Country
Occasionally, we may ask you to actively submit personal information in connection with any one of the following features or services:
Brochure Distribution (if user opts in)
Visitor Correspondence
Visitor Feedback (How the visitor found the site)
Please note that depending on the La Romita website that you are visiting, some features listed above may not be available. When available, the types and amount of personal information collected will vary depending on the activity. The actively requested personal information may include your:
Name
Home Address
Telephone Number
Email Address
No matter what method we use to collect information and no matter how we use that information, we will only collect the information deemed reasonably necessary to fulfill your online requests and our legitimate business objectives.
How La Romita Uses Collected Information
Generally, information that we collect for a particular purpose is used for that purpose only. For example, information collected from those who fill out the contact information form is used to provide La Romita a means of responding to the visitor to the page. In some instances, you may also be given the option to have your information used for an activity or service different from the activity or service that you are requesting (e.g., option in to have your name entered into a mailing list for brochures). If you choose to receive these additional services, La Romita will use your information to provide them to you.
We may also use your personal and online metrics information for our internal marketing studies, so we can constantly improve the online services we provide you and to better meet your needs. La Romita has NEVER, in 40 years, distributed our mailing list to another organization and will continue to keep it private. In the contact form section, if you refuse to provide your personal information, La Romita may be unable to reply to questions or comments.
The information that you disclose on the La Romita Websites is collected by La Romita via the web analysis service GetClicky. Information collected is used in accordance with the practices outlined above.
Questions or Complaints
If you have any questions, complaints, or comments regarding our privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with any of our websites, please contact us by postal mail at:
La Romita School of Art, Inc
P.O. Box 58219
Washington, DC 20037
Or online using the online form at www.laromita.org/contact-us
This Privacy Policy was last updated on June 29, 2005
Help Support La Romita
Thanks!
Help Support La Romita
For over 55 years La Romita has been pursuing its mission "to inspire individual creativity and artistic expression through workshops in Italy, cultural exchange, and appreciation of the arts". We feel deeply that what we are doing at La Romita - the ways that it has enriched lives and promoted appreciaition of culture and art - is worth preserving through the toughest times. You can help us to continue to pursue our mission by making a donation this season. A donation to our La Romita Foundation will go to maintaining our staff and property until it's safe to travel once again.
By helping support us through a gift (every little bit counts!) you will be an integral part of our future and the future of all who come through our doors.
If you can help us, please visit the link below
https://laromita.org/tre-aperitivi
Pin It on Pinterest
